What is the most American thing you can think of, right now?
你能想到的最具有美国特征的东西是什么  就是现在
A toilet!
一个马桶
Aurora.
奥罗拉
Who's Aurora?
奥罗拉是谁
Aurora's in her castle after she goes get food.
奥罗拉在去拿了食物之后就在她的城堡里
How many stars are on the US flag?
美国国旗上有多少颗星星
Three? Thirty nine!
三颗  三十九颗
One, two, three...
一颗  两颗  三颗
I want you to finish the song there, okay?
我想让你们把这首歌完成  好吧
"... the land of the free and the home of the..."
自由的土地和XX的家园
Lyrics?
歌词
Mighted state.
可能的国家
What is America's favorite pastime?
美国人最喜欢的娱乐活动是什么
Computery.
电脑
Computery?
电脑吗
My last question.
最好一个问题
Name one place in America that you would never, ever, ever want to live.
说出美国的一个地方  你绝对不想在那儿生活
Mexico! So hot there.
墨西哥  那儿好热的